  <Text Key="668429CB_8200">[Vật Lý] Một kiếm sư đơn độc ở tuyến đầu, bảo vệ thế giới bằng những lưỡi kiếm chém tan gió. Cô phản kích các đòn tấn công kẻ thù bằng kiếm thuật vô song, và cùng với bản sao do UB đầu tiên tạo ra, cô lao tới với tốc độ chớp nhoáng hướng về tương lai.</Text>
  <Text Key="B945395E_8201">Divine Art - Ooharai Shinatobe Kaze</Text>
  <Text Key="D0B53499_8202">[Triệu Hồi] Gây sát thương vật lý lớn cho kẻ địch phía trước. Nếu có bản sao do Shinatsu tạo ra trong đồng minh, gây thêm sát thương vật lý lớn và tăng nhẹ sát thương vật lý nhận vào. Union Burst đầu tiên sau khi trận đấu bắt đầu sẽ tăng cường mạnh mẽ tốc độ hành động của tất cả đồng minh và triệu hồi một bản sao của chính mình (bản sao này không sử dụng Union Burst).</Text>
  <Text Key="81053955_8203">►Gây $1 sát thương vật lý lên một kẻ địch.\n►Nếu có [Bản Sao của Shizuru], gây $2 sát thương vật lý lên một kẻ địch.\n►Nếu có [Bản Sao của Shizuru], tăng $3% sát thương vật lý nhận vào của một kẻ địch.\n►Lần sử dụng đầu tiên, tạo ra một bản sao.\n►Lần sử dụng đầu tiên, tăng $4% Tốc Độ Hành Động của tất cả đồng minh.</Text>
  <Text Key="1CDE420F_8204">Secret Sword - Juujin Kaze</Text>
  <Text Key="CA23FC3F_8205">Gây sát thương vật lý lớn cho kẻ địch phía trước và giảm nhẹ P.DEF của chúng. Ngoài ra, thi triển khiên phản vật lý lên bản thân và hồi phục một lượng HP vừa phải.</Text>
  <Text Key="EC8D22ED_8206">►Gây $1 sát thương vật lý lên một kẻ địch.\n►Giảm $2 P.DEF của một kẻ địch.\n►Thi triển Khiên Phản Vật Lý hấp thụ $3 sát thương.\n►Hồi phục $4 HP của bản thân.</Text>
  <Text Key="F48C364E_8207">Purifying Sword Dance</Text>
  <Text Key="D63C31E4_8208">Enters a state that reduces damage taken by 50%. This damage reduction is removed if no ally is positioned in front of self. Additionally, massively boosts own P.ATK and slightly boosts own P.CRIT DMG.</Text>
  <Text Key="1F7F98CF_8209">►Puts self in [Damage Reduction] state.\n►Boosts own P.ATK by $1.\n►Boosts own P.CRIT DMG by $2%.</Text>
  <Text Key="3A18DA3C_8210">Ama no Tsujikaze</Text>
  <Text Key="67409899_8211">Ama no Tsujikaze+</Text>
  <Text Key="CD79DEB0_8212">Immortal Sky Blade</Text>
  <Text Key="4A20AD7F_8213">Triggers when attacked by an enemy and deals moderate P.DMG to that enemy.</Text>
  <Text Key="13A91DF3_8214">►Deals $1 P.DMG to enemies who attack her.</Text>
  <Text Key="640FB36A_8215">Fortune-telling</Text>
  <Text Key="82B90FF5_8216">A medium who's skilled at fortune-telling</Text>
  <Text Key="25DFE81E_8217">[Physical] A spiritualist who fights from the midguard using a skull inhabited by the soul of her father. Aside from attacking separately from her, her father also occasionally intercepts incoming attacks.</Text>
  <Text Key="B6D68BF2_8218">Phantom Terror</Text>
  <Text Key="810D9BAD_8219">Deals moderate P.DMG to all enemies in range and lowers their P.DEF by a small amount.</Text>
  <Text Key="FCC1110F_8220">Otherworldly Beckoning</Text>
  <Text Key="0B6DAD70_8221">[Summon] Summons a skull in front of oneself, which attacks an enemy directly in front.</Text>
  <Text Key="098CAFE6_8222">Summons Shinobu's Skull Father.</Text>
  <Text Key="86B8E5C5_8223">Hungry Wraith</Text>
  <Text Key="25D386CF_8224">Lowers P.DEF of all enemies by a small amount.</Text>
  <Text Key="4E4675ED_8225">►Lowers all enemies' P.DEF by $1.</Text>
  <Text Key="C4090980_8226">Twilight Elegy</Text>
  <Text Key="C5502A2A_8227">Twilight Elegy+</Text>
  <Text Key="CC18D7A8_8228">Phantom Inferno</Text>
  <Text Key="F2EA061A_8229">Deals large P.DMG to all enemies within range, moderately lowers P.DEF, largely reduces speed, and inflicts Fear. Furthermore, receives [Spiritual Power] (various stats of the summoned Skull Father will be increased).</Text>
  <Text Key="1A2FAA8E_8230">►Deals $1 P.DMG to enemies in 850 range.\n►Lowers enemies' P.DEF in range by $2 for 18s.\n►Reduces enemies' action speed in range to 65% for 12s.\n►Inflicts Fear to enemies in range for 12s.\n►Receive Spiritual Power for 180s.</Text>
  <Text Key="4B79AD9D_8231">Otherworldly Beckoning+</Text>
  <Text Key="BD8F95D2_8232">[Summon] Summons a skull in front of oneself, which attacks an enemy directly in front. Moderate boost to P.ATK and allies' P.CRIT Rate in a radius around the frontmost ally.</Text>
  <Text Key="ABA3416F_8233">►Summons Shinobu's Skull Father.\n►Boosts allies' P.ATK in range by $1.\n►Boosts allies' P.CRIT Rate in range by $2.</Text>
  <Text Key="B00CB2FC_8234">Grim Soul Robe</Text>
  <Text Key="1D19A3F0_8235">[Physical] A spiritualist who picks off weakened enemies from the midguard. Her Union Burst, which heavily damages the most injured enemy, also deals damage to all remaining enemies if successful in slaying its target.</Text>
  <Text Key="9243E908_8236">Halloween Terror</Text>
  <Text Key="B34C2402_8237">Deals large P.DMG to the enemy with the lowest HP percentage. Deals additional moderate P.DMG to all enemies if the enemy is defeated by this skill.</Text>
  <Text Key="6AAFB7AA_8238">►Deals $1 P.DMG to an enemy.\n►Deals $2 P.DMG to all enemies.</Text>
  <Text Key="2D1F5B62_8239">Wraith Weapon</Text>
  <Text Key="46243B97_8240">Large boost to own P.ATK.</Text>
  <Text Key="21D76ADF_8241">►Boosts own P.ATK by $1.</Text>
  <Text Key="2FC88B03_8242">Hollow Scythe</Text>
  <Text Key="AA39852E_8243">Deals moderate P.DMG to all enemies in range.</Text>
  <Text Key="E6A9D31F_8244">►Deals $1 P.DMG to enemies in range.</Text>
  <Text Key="00AC64CF_8245">Netherworld Nocturne</Text>
  <Text Key="792DD89A_8246">Netherworld Nocturne+</Text>
  <Text Key="ABB34281_8247">Wraith Weapon+</Text>
  <Text Key="CD47E6B5_8248">Massive boost to own P.ATK and Large boost to own P.CRIT Rate.</Text>
  <Text Key="CBC1AE27_8249">►Boosts own P.ATK by $1 for 12s.\n►Boosts own P.CRIT Rate by $2.</Text>
