  <Text Key="E55FFC87_11250">Coral Dragon</Text>
  <Text Key="FBB17CC7_11251">A fearsome hunter of the deep sea, intensified by Luna&apos;s magic. With a honed physique, it releases a single strike of water that transforms into a blade.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A71EE073_11252">Deals large P.DMG to the first four characters in the front, moderately lowering their P.ATK. Additionally, slightly increases TP for all allies.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="1AA62F95_11253">Deals medium M.DMG to a small frontal area and greatly decreases TP.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A7F1BD29_11254">Deals medium P.DMG to a small area centered around the second character from the back, greatly lowering M.ATK.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="3D6D7CBD_11255">A gigantic golem covered in the crystallization of Luna&apos;s magic. The crystals adorning it serve as sturdy shields and become spears that pierce through everything.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A0EFAC22_11256">When the Crystal Golem receives poison, venom, curse, or burn effects, its action speed greatly decreases.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="6FB30008_11257">Removes all debuff effects on itself and greatly increases P.DEF and M.DEF. Additionally, moderately increases P.DEF and M.DEF for all allies except itself.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="7281C042_11258">Deals medium P.DMG to all enemies, inflicting stun.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="78F630CA_11259">Deals large P.DMG to enemies within a frontal area, slightly increases the P.ATK and allies&apos; M.ATK, and moderately recovers its own TP.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="89999515_11260">Crystal Golem</Text>
  <Text Key="A9F82219_11261">A sea creature rampaging in Luna&apos;s tower. Once a servant of the ancient sea god, now reduced to a purposeless destroyer.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="26CB542B_11262">Deals M.DMG to all enemies.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="F74746D4_11263">Deploys a field in a certain range that decreases P.ATK and M.DEF and inflicts continuous M.DMG.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="CEF2B27E_11264">Deals large M.DMG to the second and third characters from the front.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="AF167A92_11265">Rampaging Sea Beast</Text>
  <Text Key="CA6669DA_11266">A clown from the demon world scheming to make Luna&apos;s Tower its stage. It manipulates the lives of the audience with a cheerful smile and madness.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="A43AFA41_11267">Deals large M.DMG to all enemies and inflicts darkness status.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="520CFA1E_11268">Deals random small P.DMG to one character six times, then deals large P.DMG to all enemies. This attack becomes more accurate against characters in the front row.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="92718AB8_11269">Summons a timed bomb in a medium range in front. The bomb explodes after 8 seconds, dealing medium P.DMG to all enemies within its range. However, if the bomb&apos;s HP drops below 1% before exploding, it deals P.DMG equal to 15% of Mad Clown&apos;s maximum HP.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="144DF151_11270">Mad Clown</Text>
  <Text Key="C281C35F_11271">An ancient weapon running amok with Luna&apos;s Tower&apos;s magic. The power of ancient guardians has transformed into a curse-spreading catastrophe.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="E0087294_11272">Deals large P.DMG to all enemies and greatly decreases its own P.DEF and M.DEF.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="674CEA0D_11273">Deals medium P.DMG to all enemies within a range centered around one character in the front, moderately lowering their P.DEF. Additionally, inflicts stun.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="D661AB05_11274">Deals medium P.DMG to all enemies and inflicts curse status. If a character&apos;s HP is below 40%, curse damage is doubled.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="63D1E6EB_11275">A giant bird that has come flying seeking Luna&apos;s magic. It wields a petrifying cursed sword, accompanied by its fledglings.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="3E7FBD7D_11276">Deals large M.DMG to all non-petrified characters and petrifies them briefly. Deals damage equal to 80% of maximum HP to all petrified characters.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="546FD94D_11277">Deals small M.DMG to the first three characters from the front. Additionally, petrifies characters afflicted with poison for a long duration.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="32FF4C0C_11278">Deals medium M.DMG to characters within a frontal area and inflicts poison status. If its own HP is below 50%, knocks back all enemies and summons a Cuckoo.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="5C0B190B_11279">The Cuckoo deals small P.DMG to the character with the highest P.ATK within a frontal area and inflicts poison status. When its own HP drops below 35% of maximum HP, it moderately increases TP for the ally with the highest P.ATK and becomes incapacitated.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="86103965_11280">A mysterious creature that consumes the magic of Luna&apos;s Tower and continues to proliferate. It crushes everything indiscriminately.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="3505AB0D_11281">Deals large P.DMG to all enemies and additionally decreases P.DEF.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="017DE24B_11282">Deals P.DMG to enemies within a frontal area, greatly decreases the P.ATK of the two characters with the highest P.ATK, and further decreases their TP. Greatly decreases its own P.DEF.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="F8A034B1_11283">Deals P.DMG to the first three characters from the front and moderately increases its own P.ATK.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="BE97AC86_11284">A giant lizard mutated by Luna&apos;s magic. Its hard spike-like scales chip away at the enemy&apos;s health and armor.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="42620144_11285">Deals large P.DMG to all enemies and further decreases their TP.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="5C55592A_11286">Deals P.DMG to the first three characters from the front, deals large P.DMG to the frontmost character, and decreases their P.DEF and M.DEF.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="56FFCCEC_11287">Iwanozuchi</Text>
  <Text Key="3D809D5F_11288">Deals large P.DMG to all enemies and further decreases the P.ATK of P.ATKers. Damage is increased by 1.8x against enemies with burn status.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="D994BF4A_11289">A creature from another realm that appeared in search of Luna&apos;s magic. It plans to conquer Luna&apos;s Tower with its magic eye and followers.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="342E4C56_11290">Deals large M.DMG to all enemies and additionally decreases their M.DEF.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="E8599E1F_11291">Deals random small M.DMG to one character six times.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="412C3E53_11292">Deals medium M.DMG and inflicts long-term restraint on the third character from the back. Additionally, deals small M.DMG to all enemies.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="1AD42EE8_11293">Lord Evilly</Text>
  <Text Key="E36A0AA1_11294">A ferocious magical beast mutated by Luna&apos;s magic. Its strong fangs easily tear apart even seasoned adventurers.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="5E9EC8B2_11295">Union Burst: Deals large P.DMG to all enemies and restores its own HP.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="4DCC4B77_11296">Deals P.DMG to enemies within a rear area and inflicts stun. Additionally, decreases the P.DEF of all enemies.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="8333497F_11297">Deals P.DMG to the first three characters from the front and inflicts poison status.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="71F3559B_11298">A heavily modified human awakened by Luna&apos;s magic. The maximum output of the small reactor is enough to electrocute itself.\n</Text>
  <Text Key="BAED4810_11299">Deals large P.DMG to the first three characters from the front and inflicts paralysis. Cancels its own status enhancement effects and decreases P.DEF and M.DEF.\n</Text>
