  <Text Key="C1252DBE_151900">"Knight"...?</Text>
  <Text Key="3B45DEEC_151901">...? Do you... not remember who I am?</Text>
  <Text Key="1E403C5B_151902">I feel like I should know you...</Text>
  <Text Key="B35D3868_151903">...Hmm, I see what's happening now...</Text>
  <Text Key="9588E724_151904">A phenomenon like this... is quite interesting.</Text>
  <Text Key="FE1F3D0B_151905">──{playername}, apparently we are the only two people in here.</Text>
  <Text Key="B061AEC3_151906">But there's some people around taking a walk...</Text>
  <Text Key="0A92317A_151907">Ah, by that I meant... "people we know of".</Text>
  <Text Key="4C286C9E_151908">Seems there's no possibility of {playername}'s friends to come here.</Text>
  <Text Key="CFE54528_151909">How do you know that?</Text>
  <Text Key="2065DE38_151910">Fufu... I don't know what kind of being is doing this nor what this place is for──</Text>
  <Text Key="DF17E6AD_151911">But it seems that it couldn't get into the deepest level of my subconsciousness which usually lies dormant.</Text>
  <Text Key="0A804FFE_151912">...If it intends to hurt {playername}, then a strict correction will be needed. But if it's just playing around, then I'll look over it.</Text>
  <Text Key="E4EAD794_151913">...Or perhaps this is an opportunity to make my wishes come true. In order to make memories with him...</Text>
  <Text Key="23857929_151914">{playername}, you are a personal friend of mine so I have a favor to ask you...</Text>
  <Text Key="E7D257A5_151915">Please play "House" with me.</Text>
  <Text Key="3012A86E_151916">"House"?</Text>
  <Text Key="CF29E547_151917">Yeah. I learned it from your little friends, Mimi, Misogi and Kyouka.</Text>
  <Text Key="84124FFC_151918">...How about it?</Text>
  <Text Key="644CE244_151919">Fufu, I am glad.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C241A8A_151920">Then let's go to your house right away. Oh, before that we'll go to a shopping street first.</Text>
  <Text Key="92571825_151921">It's a married couple's shopping date♪</Text>
  <Text Key="B2DF5042_151922">Married couple?</Text>
  <Text Key="0C43890C_151923">Yes. The most common relationship between a man and a woman is called a "married couple", isn't it?</Text>
  <Text Key="9D5CB087_151924">Even if we're just playing house, we shouldn't deviate too far from the rules.</Text>
  <Text Key="BC402E6F_151925">But I don't even know your name...</Text>
  <Text Key="DD214B1E_151926">Ah, sorry about that... Hmm, that's true...</Text>
  <Text Key="7054946A_151927">Then, here's my human name. I am called "Barakieru".</Text>
  <Text Key="69151296_151928">Feel free to call me "Eru".</Text>
  <Text Key="C56C2F38_151929">"Eru"...?</Text>
  <Text Key="616D42FA_151930">Yes, Darling♪</Text>
  <Text Key="9D53ED54_151931">Then let's start from... shopping for dinner.</Text>
  <Text Key="EEE4B346_151932">In Gio Teogonia, I can immediately find eatable mud balls or flowers... I suppose that's not the case here.</Text>
  <Text Key="C3FBFD4D_151933">Are you good at cooking?</Text>
  <Text Key="AB725924_151934">A little.</Text>
  <Text Key="A55199D8_151935">Fufu, then I'll be looking forward to it...♪</Text>
  <Text Key="2533E991_151936">Rather than that...</Text>
  <Text Key="A72F2808_151937">Why are you holding my arm?</Text>
  <Text Key="A0A964CD_151938">Well we're married couples on a date♪</Text>
  <Text Key="08A93D47_151939">If I have to tell you more about my reasons right now... {playername} and Princess Pecorine would surely be suspicious of me, also...</Text>
  <Text Key="62EFD1A8_151940">It has been awhile since I last placed my feet on the ground. It'd be terrible if I were to to fall the ground and ruined the food we bought.</Text>
  <Text Key="4D8E72F0_151941">What are we buying?</Text>
  <Text Key="D9772F87_151942">On this occasion, I would like to eat a dish called "Hotpot".</Text>
  <Text Key="02E3120F_151943">Putting varied ingredients in a single big pot and sharing it with everyone... Doesn't that sound just like a happy family?</Text>
  <Text Key="054AB0C6_151944">Then we should start with a vegetable shop.</Text>
  <Text Key="E649F4D2_151945">Vegetable shop...This store specializes in vegetables.</Text>
  <Text Key="D1CF1483_151946">Cabbage, green onions, carrots... What else do we need?</Text>
  <Text Key="E6EF35FF_151947">You there, are you making a hotpot tonight? Don't forget about mushrooms! Enoki and Nishitake mushrooms are guaranteed to make your hotpot full of flavors!</Text>
  <Text Key="B7D62553_151948">Fufu, then I'll buy some.</Text>
  <Text Key="6844B0EA_151949">Yes, no problem! ...Hm? Now that I take a closer look...</Text>
