  <Text Key="B7F90831_152500">ÁÁÁÁÁÁÁ!?</Text>
  <Text Key="62BD5368_152501">T-T somehow I've made it through that rush... I wonder what would have happened if {playername} hadn't been there... Or rather, never in my dreams would I have imagined the lost and found department would be like this...</Text>
  <Text Key="D7C15C31_152502">That's right. All lost items from all over Landosol are collected here. And it's the capital, so you can imagine how many live here...</Text>
  <Text Key="AC81601D_152503">No one knows about it, but there are an incredible number of lost items... It's like they say, little by little, it makes a big difference...</Text>
  <Text Key="31498627_152504">No wonder there were so many huge warehouses. I didn't expect a lost items department would be this harsh. And we got yelled at nonstop by the people coming in.</Text>
  <Text Key="6FC3E773_152505">Good work, everyone! I have a meeting with the Commander about expanding our warehouses, so I won't be back by the regular time, but I'll leave the rest to you!</Text>
  <Text Key="6502BE39_152506">Huh? Really? Well then, I guess we'll go with our senpais...</Text>
  <Text Key="202CF629_152507">We just finished a night shift, so we're heading home early... the rest's on you~...</Text>
  <Text Key="4D3B95A6_152508">No way, please wait a second, pals! Don't just leave the newbies behind! Isn't this supposed to be a homely workplace?! Hey!</Text>
  <Text Key="78D55789_152509">Aaah, they're gone... But we've finished dealing with all the people in line waiting for a consultation, so maybe things will be fine.</Text>
  <Text Key="25A6E2EF_152510">...Though there's still a mountain of documents that we've failed to compile on time.</Text>
  <Text Key="A6AB567E_152511">Hmm...! Somehow, that's a wrap on the paperwork. It's almost time to go pal, so all that's left is to close the counter and wait for the section chief to return.</Text>
  <Text Key="05F45421_152512">Um, apologies to bother you outside of reception time. I'd like you to check if you've received some black gloves.</Text>
  <Text Key="F0D3D69D_152513">Huh? Umm... Ugh?! Even just from the things that arrived today, there's a lot of matching descriptions.</Text>
  <Text Key="EB07E37A_152514">If you do know you're outside reception time then just come tomorrow, pal~ I'm sure he'll be fine without some gloves for a night, so I'll just have to convince him to come back later...</Text>
  <Text Key="74C1564D_152515">Eeeh?! You're going to listen to this man's request? You do know reception hours are already over, right, pal?</Text>
  <Text Key="56B1C64A_152516">...The old man came all the way here because he wanted help? So you think it'd be wrong not to help him...?</Text>
  <Text Key="82961BCB_152517">That's, umm...</Text>
  <Text Key="8A703AB2_152518">...You're right. Sorry, pal, but can I ask you to do the paperwork? I'll run to the warehouse and grab every black glove that came in recently!</Text>
  <Text Key="0432418C_152519">Old man, help me check them out when I return. There's a chance yours is among them!</Text>
  <Text Key="283D4A9B_152520">Sorry... and thank you...</Text>
  <Text Key="CD0D6BC4_152521">These...! These are the gloves I was looking for...! Thank goodness, you really had them.</Text>
  <Text Key="CD41EEA2_152522">Wow, that's great, pal! Are they, like, expensive or something?</Text>
  <Text Key="14063F55_152523">No, they're handmade. My wife knitted them for me a long time ago.</Text>
  <Text Key="A2D0F11D_152524">I meant to take good care of them, but I still managed to lose them... I guess I'm getting too old... It's been a long time since she died.</Text>
  <Text Key="1AA543A5_152525">So it was a memento of your late wife... I'm so glad someone kind delivered it here!</Text>
  <Text Key="DD27AE7B_152526">Yeah, you can say that again. Besides, you two were also a huge help, so thank you. As expected, the Royal Knights of NIGHTMARE are quite reliable.</Text>
  <Text Key="44D8DE6A_152527">Next time, please be careful not to drop them, pal!</Text>
  <Text Key="2389CE3E_152528">It's not that... I'm feeling a little guilty. I thought they were just "a pair of gloves", so I felt like I could deal with it later. I had no idea they were something so important to him that he couldn't get them back even if he paid money.</Text>
  <Text Key="B027C9AF_152529">If we hadn't given him a consultation, I'm sure that old man would've felt restless after returning home. Even if it was just for a night, that would be wrong.</Text>
  <Text Key="79D05587_152530">The Royal Knights of NIGHTMARE are always there to help the citizens. Thanks to you setting an example for me, pal, I was able to remember my original calling.</Text>
  <Text Key="6CF3FF2A_152531">Getting rid of villains and looking after lost items are equally important jobs♪</Text>
  <Text Key="3B68B66C_152532">...Thanks for working with me today, pal! I'll do my best to get myself fired up and be in charge at the lost items front desk tomorrow!</Text>
  <Text Key="09F41024_152533">With {playername}'s help, Matsuri was one step closer to becoming a full-fledged member of the Royal Knights of NIGHTMARE.</Text>
  <Text Key="29FD521B_152534">Knight Captain</Text>
  <Text Key="1234F276_152535">I'm the part-timer</Text>
  <Text Key="2132BC4E_152536">Lost Item Section Man 1</Text>
  <Text Key="91DA9B89_152537">Lost Item Section Man 2</Text>
  <Text Key="42BB50A6_152538">Lost&amp;Found Chief</Text>
  <Text Key="75CABE9D_152539">Lost Item Section Men 1 and 2</Text>
  <Text Key="C1E5E92D_152540">For now, let's deal with it!</Text>
  <Text Key="7F0304F8_152541">I'll deal with this guy</Text>
  <Text Key="9E2D970C_152542">Do you recall where you might've dropped them?</Text>
  <Text Key="8BFFB2EF_152543">Tired?</Text>
  <Text Key="E1B12A18_152544">This is clearly a dream</Text>
  <Text Key="D8285AF2_152545">Matsuri remembered the original calling that led her to join the Royal Knights of NIGHTMARE. With a change of heart, she found herself working even harder with {playername}.</Text>
  <Text Key="12A9FDCD_152546">It's already been a week since we started working at the Lost&amp;Found department~ It was tough at first, but once I got the hang of it everything felt smoother!</Text>
  <Text Key="02CDB53C_152547">Yesterday, I returned a lost item and someone thanked me, so I'm starting to feel like this is a worthwhile job! At this rate, I'll become a full fledged Lost&amp;Found clerk!</Text>
  <Text Key="872F7E95_152548">I see, I see. I'm glad to hear that you're working hard and staying positive. ...Honestly, I didn't expect that.</Text>
  <Text Key="613540D0_152549">Ah, Captain! What's wrong, pal? You're in the Lost&amp;Found department, did you lose something?</Text>
