  <Text Key="36421339_167000">T-Thank you very much... Kyaaaaaa!</Text>
  <Text Key="04A6774A_167001">T-T-Touch my hand?! What are you doing?! That's not how you do things, Kishi-san! If you do that... I can't help but make sounds like that! I mean, I'll take some water!</Text>
  <Text Key="DF5D09B9_167002">*Gulp gulp*... Ah, ahhh! This water is so good... *gulp gulp* Nn, ngh?! Guguh... *cough cough*!</Text>
  <Text Key="5123E221_167003">Ugh, ugh, now it's in my nose... Hey, p-please don't look at me with that face~!</Text>
  <Text Key="461593A0_167004">KHHHHHH~ This is so embarrassing... And it's all because of what I said earlier~</Text>
  <Text Key="671A2BCC_167005">The feelings I have for Kishi-san... I LOVE HIM!</Text>
  <Text Key="44147271_167006">You can say whatever you want! Both Rei-sama and Kishi-san are MINE!</Text>
  <Text Key="EFD25575_167007">Ughhhh. I know it was just a heat-of-the-moment argument, but to say something like that in front of Kishi-san...! It's all because of that perverted woman with terrible fashion sense! It's all Kanon-san's fault!</Text>
  <Text Key="79E1A33B_167008">And Kishi-san is just being... Kishi-san! I confessed, plain as day, and he doesn't even react? Just keeps on acting like the world's perfectly normal!? He's so unfazed that it's pissing me off...!</Text>
  <Text Key="3275B80D_167009">...Hah. I wonder what he actually thinks... about what I said back then...</Text>
  <Text Key="820F3FB0_167010">Maybe I should be even bolder and press him for an answer myself...? No, no! There's no way I can do that! I want to ask! But I can't! WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!</Text>
  <Text Key="8CE0080B_167011">N-No, it's nothing! I'll be going to rest over there! Take your time, Kishi-san, see ya!</Text>
  <Text Key="2985B12E_167012">Aww, I ran away in the end... I'm so pathetic. Ugh... this is such a downer...</Text>
  <Text Key="FC4C38ED_167013">*sigh*... Well, I should've expected this. It's just how I really feel. No matter how stubborn I am, no matter how angry I get, I can't fool myself.</Text>
  <Text Key="8991087F_167014">I love Rei-sama. As for Kishi-san... I also love him.</Text>
  <Text Key="9348AA89_167015">There are two types of "love" inside of me. It's like they're fighting a tight tug of war inside my heart. Maybe it's because they're equally strong feelings...</Text>
  <Text Key="BB3B9A21_167016">However, Rei-sama seems to also have... special feelings for Kishi-san. Huh? Wait, does that mean Rei-sama and I are... LOVE RIVALS?!</Text>
  <Text Key="6F46B5B3_167017">No, no, no! That's absolutely impossible! I mean on the other hand I also really really love Rei-sama! I'm rooting for her!</Text>
  <Text Key="E4544278_167018">...But, maybe that in and of itself is not a good idea. Do I really have to choose? My feelings for Rei-sama. My feelings for Kishi-san. If I had to choose one... THAT'D BE JUST IMPOSSIBLE! ...Uh, what?</Text>
  <Text Key="793B9F58_167019">Those two... What are they doing? Are they arguing about something?</Text>
  <Text Key="C0525B8F_167020">I told you, didn't I?! I'm giving you this meat!</Text>
  <Text Key="DEC523ED_167021">And I told you! I'm not hungry right now!</Text>
  <Text Key="FC56D8B5_167022">Liar! I've definitely heard it! The sound of your hungry big belly, that is! I caught some good meat during the morning hunt. Feel free to eat it.</Text>
  <Text Key="80BDAAA7_167023">Huuuuuh?! Y-You must've misheard or something! I'm going hunting soon too. If I take meat now, it'll just weigh me down!</Text>
  <Text Key="D7A1484A_167024">Oof... classic "even a dog wouldn't bite" kind of fight. So there are people like this in Gio Gehenna, too. People who can't be honest.</Text>
  <Text Key="06EC33C8_167025">I'm just saying this because I have some leftovers, you know? Geez, you've always been so difficult! Ever since we were little!</Text>
  <Text Key="65A34E60_167026">Because you have leftovers? Are you trying to give me your scraps? You always have to say one thing too many! Ever since we were little!</Text>
  <Text Key="647F6C58_167027">That said, those two sure are close. They have a wild look... If they paid more attention to their clothes, they would look so fashionable.</Text>
  <Text Key="6C732EE2_167028">In the first place, what's with that outfit of yours?! How disgraceful!</Text>
  <Text Key="623FC3E4_167029">Oh? Are they talking about clothes now?! Isn't this a first for Gio Gehenna? That's right! Keep going, tell her!</Text>
  <Text Key="842A842F_167030">You're going on hunts, yet you're still wearing those rags! The Gio Gehenna's way is to hunt NAKED! It's the norm to use your wild body as a weapon to go after your prey!</Text>
  <Text Key="37845681_167031">No, no, why would anyone think that?! Is she really serious about going at it naked?! Hunting's totally different from going to a hot spring, you know! Wait, this is Kanon-san's fashion spreading! Ugh, this sucks!</Text>
  <Text Key="E5C8156D_167032">Wh-What era are you even living in? There's no one living like that nowadays, you know?! You're not cute at all wearing those clothes!</Text>
  <Text Key="C35057EF_167033">Yes, that's right! There's so many cute clothes you could wear beyond those! Go and tell her more!</Text>
  <Text Key="2E6DDB53_167034">HUUUUUUUUH?! What do you mean, "cute"? It's a given that clothes should serve a usage for practicality first! Besides, do I even need to wear them if they'd never fit me?!</Text>
  <Text Key="25DBFAF2_167035">...Who was it that decided they wouldn't look good on you... Geez, you're just SO dishonest! You're always so "tsun-tsun", but never "dere" at all!</Text>
  <Text Key="03D6D706_167036">H-How and why did things turn out like this... You shouldn't just decide something doesn't suit you like that...</Text>
  <Text Key="F31B631F_167037">Ugh... You're the one who doesn't understand how I feel! We've been together for so long, why is it always like this?!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2C3C881_167038">Tch, do as you please, then. You idiot.</Text>
  <Text Key="E91467BB_167039">As for that man...! What are you doing just letting her leave like that?! Sure, I think that woman's got an attitude, but telling someone who's being stubborn that they're "dishonest" is the biggest landmine!</Text>
  <Text Key="B49531EE_167040">I mean, I'm aware... of that kind of behaviour better than anyone...</Text>
  <Text Key="E3FBC7B5_167041">AAAAAAAAAAH, COME ON! JUST GO AND CHASE AFTER HER! DON'T JUST LEAVE THAT GIRL ALONE!</Text>
  <Text Key="C21E9901_167042">W-Whoa whoa, Kishi-san? S-Since when were you...?! ...D-Did you come chasing after me?</Text>
  <Text Key="23159DD4_167043">...! Th-Thank you very much... I'm sorry for worrying you.</Text>
  <Text Key="6749145B_167044">Oh, crap... I'm so happy... So happy that I can't even hide my smile! Wait, no! I shouldn't be happy! That's exactly the problem here, Kishi-san! That's why I'm stuck wavering between you and Rei-sama!</Text>
  <Text Key="632B1E6D_167045">Umm... well, this is a continuation of what I was saying earlier. Watching that exchange between those two childhood friends who were fighting... I really got the sense that this world just doesn't care about fashion at all.</Text>
  <Text Key="9891CBA0_167046">If that were all, I could just chalk it up to "oh well, different world"... But watching those two... it didn't feel like someone else's problem. ...I guess people's hearts are the same no matter what world they're in.</Text>
  <Text Key="0BDA9BBB_167047">That's why it's even more frustrating... I understand that because it's a world that is based on hunting, you want clothes that are easy to move in, but I think they could be a little more considerate about their clothing.</Text>
  <Text Key="674C19D4_167048">What do you think, Kishi-san? If it's all about practicality... does that mean looking cute doesn't matter at all?</Text>
  <Text Key="F9F5DCD1_167049">I really think how you look can bring about a lot of positives. Does fashion just get in the way of functionality...?</Text>
