  <Text Key="49FC501E_168600">P-Please wait! Thrashing about like that will only... Kyah!</Text>
  <Text Key="ED9C4F8C_168601">Yes... had the waters been deeper, this body would not have risen... and together, we would have sunk to the riverbed.</Text>
  <Text Key="E21C670D_168602">But it is thanks to you that I was able to rise from the river. My deepest thanks, Kishi-sama.</Text>
  <Text Key="E9776089_168603">Yes. For now, let us return to a place where the sun shines.</Text>
  <Text Key="600E30EA_168604">...Kishi-sama? You are preparing a fire... but whatever for?</Text>
  <Text Key="74D82584_168605">Th-That is... My deepest apologies, Kishi-sama.</Text>
  <Text Key="F9E22FA5_168606">I appreciate the sentiment, but... the coldness you felt... is not because of what just happened. It is because I am an undead.</Text>
  <Text Key="26CE012D_168607">...B-But truly, your concern delights me! And even if my body feels no ill, my garments must still be dried.</Text>
  <Text Key="3D068DA8_168608">So... umm... I... wish to take off my clothes. Forgive me, but might I trouble you for assistance...?</Text>
  <Text Key="0B37DEA8_168609">Thank you... ordinarily, I rely on Lului and the others for such things, so...</Text>
  <Text Key="2159DF61_168610">Yes, umm... if you would but undo the buttons at my back, that will suffice. The rest, I can manage alone...</Text>
  <Text Key="20B95AF0_168611">Huh...? You want to lend me your jacket...? N-No, that is... for a lady to borrow a gentleman's garment... is that not shameless...?</Text>
  <Text Key="66FEF409_168612">...Then, I shall accept your kindness. Umm... Thank you very much, Kishi-sama...</Text>
  <Text Key="D16944D2_168613">And so, Violet and {playername} sat in silence for a time, drying their clothes.</Text>
  <Text Key="F04B539B_168614">Forgive me, for having shown you something so unseemly before... Mmm...</Text>
  <Text Key="139DD02D_168615">Even if it was but my back... to bare my skin before a gentleman, before Kishi-sama himself... I could die of shame...! I only pray there were no scars upon it...</Text>
  <Text Key="FBE07B23_168616">...Yet the coat I borrowed from Kishi-sama was so very warm...</Text>
  <Text Key="EB272153_168617">And the hand he offered me in the water just before... All that Kishi-sama bestows is steeped in warmth.</Text>
  <Text Key="348A5C57_168618">It is as if I have been waiting impatiently for that hand all this time... Could this be... another memory of my past...?</Text>
  <Text Key="9D9FA848_168619">...In the first place, what was it that I felt in the water earlier...?</Text>
  <Text Key="FE4EDE27_168620">Y-Yes! ...Um, Kishi-sama? That fish in your hand... is it...</Text>
  <Text Key="B53957FB_168621">Kishi-sama... You must have been worried about what I said back then all this time...</Text>
  <Text Key="EA6B2FAA_168622">...Thank you. Then I shall partake, as you so kindly offer.</Text>
  <Text Key="8685CAC0_168623">In Landosol... I assume this is how you eat fishes?</Text>
  <Text Key="CE021CF1_168624">We do not get many "living" fishes in Gio Nivlhel. Besides, when it comes to cooking them with fire... well, all we really have are will-o'-the-wisps.</Text>
  <Text Key="20E9ECEB_168625">In our world, many beings like ghosts and zombies can go without eating day after day... Perhaps that is why meals are so irregular, and cooking so haphazard.</Text>
  <Text Key="A9DE61AD_168626">However... that is merely the way of Gio Nivlhel. Right now, I too would like to try this fish.</Text>
  <Text Key="D0996078_168627">If I could... I would eat until I was full.</Text>
  <Text Key="3EE8D11C_168628">Well then, time to dig in... Hamph...</Text>
  <Text Key="41679510_168629">...Hamph, hamph... Delicious...</Text>
  <Text Key="5103FC0B_168630">Fresh... the flesh of a fish that was alive only moments ago, grilled to perfection. Plump, tender... simple, and yet so very delicious...</Text>
  <Text Key="A037A1F5_168631">As I feared, I am unable to eat like Kishi-sama does... Yet I can savor it all the same.</Text>
  <Text Key="93BABB25_168632">Though my body is cold, I can still love living things, feel joy, and share in their emotions...</Text>
  <Text Key="0A31910B_168633">If these feelings I bear for Kishi-sama cannot be restrained... then at the very least, I wish to draw closer to him...</Text>
  <Text Key="77A15077_168634">With hands that share his warmth... I want to touch him...!</Text>
  <Text Key="E65FAF5E_168635">Yes. I am sure that even Grace is worried for us by now. But... I am sure that the road ahead will be fine.</Text>
  <Text Key="5B5913BB_168636">Violet became aware of the wish stirring within her. Though she knew it would not be easily fulfilled, a glimmer of hope for the future had begun to shine in her eyes.</Text>
  <Text Key="57A32D91_168637">*Tôi nắm lấy tay Violet*</Text>
  <Text Key="CCFE9856_168638">*Tôi cố gắng chống đỡ để nổi lên mặt nước*</Text>
  <Text Key="3A8E1A74_168639">May mà nước không sâu...</Text>
  <Text Key="00544426_168640">Chúng ta về trại thôi</Text>
  <Text Key="2B4E3AAE_168641">Tay em lạnh quá, Violet</Text>
  <Text Key="605DB54A_168642">Vì vậy em phải sưởi ấm cẩn thận mới được...</Text>
  <Text Key="FC8CCB8F_168643">Violet...?</Text>
  <Text Key="FBDB1DA9_168644">Tôi nướng nó luôn rồi, muốn ăn không...?</Text>
  <Text Key="76AB8964_168645">Ở Gio Nivlhel, mấy người không ăn cá sống sao?</Text>
  <Text Key="09F86BFA_168646">Ăn xong chúng ta về lâu đài thôi</Text>
  <Text Key="E94CD1CB_168647">Ngày công chúa Violet trở về Gio Nivlhel sau nhiệm vụ ở Landosol, nó đã mời {playername} đến một buổi tiệc trà để bày tỏ lòng biết ơn.</Text>
  <Text Key="F8C19409_168648">Cho phép tôi cảm ơn anh một lần nữa, Kishi-sama -- không chỉ vì dẫn tôi đi xem Landosol, mà còn vì hộ tống tôi suốt đường về Lâu Đài Cá voi Lớn.</Text>
  <Text Key="91693C41_168649">Thế giới của anh còn tuyệt vời hơn những gì tôi được nghe. Người dân tràn đầy sinh khí, cây cỏ tươi mát rực rỡ... và những chú mèo thì đơn giản là đáng yêu quá đi.</Text>
