  <Text Key="7759311A_58150">...M-Mitsuki-san! Cảm ơn cô đã luôn quan tâm đến bà ngoại tôi!</Text>
  <Text Key="D3681936_58151">...Q-Quan tâm đến bà ngoại cô...? Tôi...?</Text>
  <Text Key="5CBDA433_58152">Vâng! Bà ngoại kể với tôi qua điện thoại. Rằng Mitsuki-san nhà bên cạnh luôn lo lắng cho bà sống một mình, nên bà giả vờ có khiếu nại chỉ để đến thăm.</Text>
  <Text Key="7F88DB0D_58153">Bà ngoại lúc nào cũng nói về cô với niềm vui thích! Bà ấy vui mừng đến mức cô như là một đứa cháu gái thứ hai vậy, Mitsuki-san!</Text>
  <Text Key="A42F400E_58154">Chính vì vậy... tôi đã muốn gặp cô từ lâu lắm rồi, Mitsuki-san! Để tôi cũng có thể cảm ơn cô vì tất cả những gì cô đã làm!</Text>
  <Text Key="38BEB2DA_58155">Thật sự...! Cảm ơn cô rất nhiều!</Text>
  <Text Key="9F8B6D0B_58156">Đó là... có lẽ cô đã hiểu nhầm điều gì đó, tôi nghĩ vậy. Thôi, tôi còn việc phải làm.</Text>
  <Text Key="352918D6_58157">...Hẹn gặp lại.</Text>
  <Text Key="0046666B_58158">Vâng! Gặp lại sau!</Text>
  <Text Key="C5571006_58159">Và thế là, đây là câu chuyện đằng sau mối liên hệ định mệnh giữa Mitsuki và Bà Tera. Và rồi, cuộc gặp gỡ của cô ấy với Mari. ...Có lẽ họ thực sự cũng như vậy trong kiếp trước.</Text>
  <Text Key="6F4FC90F_58160">Không, chắc chắn rồi.</Text>
  <Text Key="14C9EB9C_58161">Wanted Woman, Louise Marie</Text>
  <Text Key="53C655D6_58162">Another Genius Alchemist</Text>
  <Text Key="C1C19DE0_58163">17 Year Old Grandmother</Text>
  <Text Key="A06B245A_58164">Iroha&apos;s Oedo Travelogue</Text>
  <Text Key="4097A386_58165">A Comrade Who Shook My Heart Anew</Text>
  <Text Key="71A6015B_58166">Alces and Twilight!</Text>
  <Text Key="CDDCEB03_58167">Mixed “Ultimate Transmutation”!</Text>
  <Text Key="897669BD_58168">The Back-alley Doctor &amp; The Alchemist</Text>
  <Text Key="68CEBB90_58169">About 10 years ago in a certain town -- a girl with deer antlers and an old woman were standing in front of an alchemy pot.</Text>
  <Text Key="AA4AB65F_58170">&quot;Original Transmutation&quot;!</Text>
  <Text Key="10C8E967_58171">...Aha♪ I&apos;ve done it! I did it, Grandma!</Text>
  <Text Key="4CF2A419_58172">My, that&apos;s amazing, Rui-chan! I can&apos;t believe your first attempt at alchemy was successful!</Text>
  <Text Key="70198C8A_58173">Wait, WHAT?! That’s a... Rank 15 Transmutation—a Golden Pendant! Even seasoned alchemists can’t make that easily!</Text>
  <Text Key="D4963E75_58174">Hehe, hey, Grandma? I wonder if I can become an alchemist just like you?</Text>
  <Text Key="09FC8794_58175">Hehe, of course you can. I guarantee it. After all, Rui-chan, you’re even more of a genius than I am!</Text>
  <Text Key="69686F30_58176">...Wasn’t it obvious?</Text>
  <Text Key="71AED359_58177">...Mnyah. Hehe... That’s right, I’m a genius. The genius alchemist, Lady Louise Marie... Mnyah...</Text>
  <Text Key="3A3C5BF6_58178">Uwah... even in her dreams, her self-confidence is sky-high. Rui-chan doesn’t seem stressed at all—her sleep must be amazing.</Text>
  <Text Key="A89A89A9_58179">Actually, she hasn&apos;t woken up at all for a while now. Yet she asked me to wake her up because she had something important to do today.</Text>
  <Text Key="8B0AE8BE_58180">Heeeey, Iroha. Don&apos;t just rummage under Rui-chan&apos;s bed. Help me wake her up instead...</Text>
  <Text Key="82F74035_58181">Okaaaay, leave it to Iroha! Then here I go! Ready and...</Text>
  <Text Key="B2555365_58182">Daaance in the... FRAGRANCEEEEE♪♪</Text>
  <Text Key="5F2AAE2F_58183">...Ehehehe, I’m such a... genius. Mnyah...</Text>
  <Text Key="184418A7_58184">Mmm, she’s not waking up. Guess Iroha has no choice but to unleash it... Iroha&apos;s best move!! ...So with that said.</Text>
  <Text Key="C1A54DB1_58185">HORNY DEATH GRIP--GO!!</Text>
  <Text Key="D2A2F659_58186">EEEEK!?</Text>
  <Text Key="E81BD3D6_58187">Rui-chan! Good morning!</Text>
  <Text Key="3222634C_58188">Wha-... I-Iroha-chan?! Don&apos;t I always tell you not to grip on my antlers...! I’m super sensitive there... It makes me all tingly... haauugh...</Text>
  <Text Key="6ECB6D96_58189">For someone claiming it’s her weak spot, you sure sound a little too happy about it. ...Rui-chan. Please spare me this R-18 show so early in the morning. It’s bad for Iroha&apos;s education.</Text>
  <Text Key="FF393434_58190">Why am I getting scolded here?! ...Wait, I’m not happy about anything!</Text>
  <Text Key="A5C244E4_58191">Nngh... s-shiver shiver shiver... Get off of me already, you ruffian girl!</Text>
  <Text Key="61F32F5B_58192">Man, you&apos;re making me blush~♪</Text>
  <Text Key="76365A55_58193">That was NOT a praise!</Text>
  <Text Key="472D0707_58194">Glad to see you&apos;re energetic today too. Anyway, Rui-chan, you sure you can waste time?</Text>
  <Text Key="8B59BAE1_58195">Huuuh? Why, what time is it... Ahh!? It&apos;s already this late!!</Text>
  <Text Key="755A2516_58196">Today is the best day of my life, the day I&apos;ve ever dreamed of... MY FIRST DATE WITH {playername}-KUUUUUUUUUN!!!!!</Text>
  <Text Key="EB89998B_58197">No, all you two are doing is shopping for alchemic ingredients, right? Well, I guess it&apos;s fine... Hehe.</Text>
  <Text Key="1DFBF578_58198">Canteen, check. Wallet, check. Gummy bears, check. Chocolate, check. Acorns, check. A handkerchief, tissues, bandages... All that&apos;s left, is a bug net and an insect cage!! FINISH!!</Text>
  <Text Key="3B39086E_58199">Hey, Iroha. Sorry to burst your bubble while you&apos;re so eager to get out and about, but you&apos;re staying home with me.</Text>
