  <Text Key="49E7442B_18800">Yeah, everyone, you're startin' to get the hang of it. Come now, let's take a mighty step further. First, here you go.</Text>
  <Text Key="36FA6854_18801">Aha! What a cute stuffed animal! Maho-sensei, was this handmade by you?</Text>
  <Text Key="A52BC095_18802">Sure did. This lil' one here's Bedivere, that one's Agravaine, and this sweetie is...</Text>
  <Text Key="5496BB18_18803">We don't need to hear their names. More importantly, what on earth are you planning to use stuffed animals for?</Text>
  <Text Key="2320733A_18804">Now, now, no need to be rushin' me. I'm going to be settin' a mighty example, so watch closely. *Glide and sway*, Kururinpa~☆</Text>
  <Text Key="D3A11BD3_18805">Huh?! She's walking around with a stuffed animal on her head!</Text>
  <Text Key="72383438_18806">What's more, the stuffed animal isn't even shaking. Just what kind of balance does she have...</Text>
  <Text Key="148DB80F_18807">Come now, you too! Be makin' sure you don't drop this mighty little one～</Text>
  <Text Key="F52F32A3_18808">Even if you say that... *Glide and sway*, *Glide and sw-...AAAAH! I can't do it! It'll fall off right away!</Text>
  <Text Key="16718BDE_18809">Of course this'd be impossible... Wait, HUH?!</Text>
  <Text Key="D5B5DAD0_18810">*Glide and sway*, *glide and sway*... Kururinpa~☆ *Glide and sway*, *glide and sway*... Kururinpa~☆</Text>
  <Text Key="CEF766A2_18811">Th-That country girl... she's making it look so easy! Wh-Why...?!</Text>
  <Text Key="AACD29C4_18812">Hmm, I wonder if it's because my legs and core got stronger from everyday work and combat?</Text>
  <Text Key="1F22DC00_18813">Normally, I'd hate the idea of having gained some muscle, but I'm surprised they're being put to good use like this.</Text>
  <Text Key="8507B8FD_18814">*Glide and sway*, *Glide and sw*-... KYAH!</Text>
  <Text Key="BCD7F2BA_18815">I-I'm sorry... I didn't see where I was going...</Text>
  <Text Key="CDC19DD4_18816">It's fine. Hey, why don't you forget about the stuffed animal for a moment and just focus on maintaining your posture? By there, try to progress little by little.</Text>
  <Text Key="E006AA2A_18817">Y-Yeah, I'll try. First, my posture... Then, little by little... Ah, um...</Text>
  <Text Key="07E1C735_18818">That was good! Keep it up!</Text>
  <Text Key="BA089E7F_18819">...Hey, if you don't mind, could you teach me the steps, too?</Text>
  <Text Key="9F1358E3_18820">Yes, of course. Then, let's go at this together! *Glide and sway*, *glide and sway*...</Text>
  <Text Key="9975BF64_18821">You're just a country bumpkin, yet you're getting so carried away! I'll just fake a stumble and throw her off her game. Let's see how you handle that you potato smelling bumpkin!</Text>
  <Text Key="D1A92A80_18822">*Glide and sway*, *glide and swaaaa... Aaaah, oh no, I tripped!!!!</Text>
  <Text Key="38A07FFA_18823">Kururinpaaaaa~☆</Text>
  <Text Key="D2EC7FA6_18824">She dodged?! L-Let me try that again...!</Text>
  <Text Key="088CE2C7_18825">H-How is she dodging me?!</Text>
  <Text Key="C8EF480E_18826">...Hold up, my Darlin' Prince. Let us be waitin' and see. Be prepared to be mighty jumpin' in if something be happenin'.</Text>
  <Text Key="CEEE7F82_18827">*pant pant*... Why... why is someone like me losing to a country bumpkin like you... AAH!</Text>
  <Text Key="B08AA741_18828">Kururin... PAAAA~!</Text>
  <Text Key="A74EFE92_18829">KYAAAH... H-Huh...?</Text>
  <Text Key="FF3D2B33_18830">Phew, that was close. Are you okay? Hurt anywhere?</Text>
  <Text Key="553236F4_18831">Ah, ugh... O-Of course I'm fine! More importantly, could you let me go already?</Text>
  <Text Key="69DC4294_18832">Oh my, I'm so sorry.</Text>
  <Text Key="5638645C_18833">What the heck... I tried to pull something underhanded and it didn't even work. And then she goes and helps me?! Ugh, this is so humiliating... At this rate, I'll be the laughingstock of high society</Text>
  <Text Key="8EE0D2F9_18834">Um, I'm sorry... for causing you all sorts of trouble.</Text>
  <Text Key="054CEC12_18835">Don't worry about it. You were trying so hard that your legs got all tangled up, weren't you? However... if you get hurt, you won't be able to dance beautifully at the ball. Make sure to be careful!</Text>
  <Text Key="9C1F5DD5_18836">I-It's not like you have to tell me! And for the record, I'm totally going to surpass you!</Text>
  <Text Key="252D3224_18837">Sure! Let's do our best until the very end!</Text>
  <Text Key="9019E176_18838">My, my~ Ain't this just the sweetest lil' picture of youthful spirit. Why, even ol' Maho-sensei's feelin' mighty fired up now!</Text>
  <Text Key="B56D700F_18839">Now then, everyone... Let's be doin' a Kururinpa~☆ One-Thousand Strike Drill!</Text>
  <Text Key="3BC63949_18840">EEEEHHHHHHH?!</Text>
  <Text Key="22834302_18841">Afterwards, inspired by Lima's dedication, the other participants helped each other through the tough lessons, and all of them passed the exam.</Text>
  <Text Key="EDD02E46_18842">...Let's work hard together!</Text>
  <Text Key="2D532A03_18843">My job is to help you and the others, Lima-chan</Text>
  <Text Key="2D88D700_18844">You look very happy, somehow</Text>
  <Text Key="551984A8_18845">This girl is Lima-chan</Text>
  <Text Key="2CDBA762_18846">That looks dangerous, I'll go stop her</Text>
  <Text Key="29C7386B_18847">Participants</Text>
  <Text Key="B346AA81_18848">The day after successfully completing their deportment lesson, Lima and the others waited in anticipation for the next lesson to be announced.</Text>
  <Text Key="3457B0A4_18849">Now then, I wonder what kind of lesson is next? I'm already looking forward to it!</Text>
