  <Text Key="9532573F_169250">Huh?</Text>
  <Text Key="A47783B5_169251">SO DAMN BORIIIIIIIIIIING!!!</Text>
  <Text Key="2C56F784_169252">What was that?! WHAT&apos;S WRONG WITH THAT GIRL!? I went out of my way to prepare a situation that she would love, and she&apos;s all like, &quot;It&apos;s about time we call it a day~&quot;?! Chicken much!?</Text>
  <Text Key="DEDCCA29_169253">What&apos;s more, she could tell without issue that was a dream; the memory alteration didn’t even budge her one bit. Her resistance is way too high! Is she bugged!?</Text>
  <Text Key="AAC7D269_169254">Relax</Text>
  <Text Key="1899FB45_169255">RELAX!? HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO RELAX!? I’ve got my pride too, y’know! I haven’t had any fun yet! There’s no way I’m letting it end like this! I’m gonna give her a dream she’ll NEVER forget!!</Text>
  <Text Key="8038E9D1_169256">UWAAAAaaaahhhh...!?</Text>
  <Text Key="19BC820E_169257">Eh!? T-This dream again? I thought it was over...</Text>
  <Text Key="47CF838A_169258">...Wha... What&apos;s this? My head&apos;s spinning...</Text>
  <Text Key="C093B284_169259">And that&apos;s not all... I-I feel like I&apos;m being pulled innnnnn—!</Text>
  <Text Key="44C5C22A_169260">Wakana-chan...</Text>
  <Text Key="9D56B6DC_169261">Ah... Se.. Sen-pai...?</Text>
  <Text Key="DF95A84A_169262">...Where are we...? It&apos;s dark... And... this warm sensation is...</Text>
  <Text Key="19048298_169263">──Eh!? W-WHAAAAAAAA-...!!?</Text>
  <Text Key="71586F2C_169264">W-Why!? Isn&apos;t this... a locker!? And I&apos;m inside with senpai...</Text>
  <Text Key="703C25AE_169265">T-This situation... is impossible! Which means...</Text>
  <Text Key="F2B46397_169266">A dream! This is a dream, isn&apos;t it!?</Text>
  <Text Key="CBAC272A_169267">I-I&apos;m so sorry, Senpai... Even if it was an accident... Someone like me, getting this close to you...</Text>
  <Text Key="294F504D_169268">Let&apos;s get out of here</Text>
  <Text Key="5C215CEF_169269">...R-Right. Though... part of me doesn’t really want to...</Text>
  <Text Key="3C40037F_169270">W-What&apos;s this...? The door... won&apos;t open...?</Text>
  <Text Key="2EE92D6C_169271">It&apos;s not stuck either... it simply won&apos;t budge...!</Text>
  <Text Key="8A4BB4DB_169272">Then, we&apos;ll just have to wait for help to come...</Text>
  <Text Key="06311B81_169273">N-No way! This is bad...!</Text>
  <Text Key="CBAB76F3_169274">Help... I mean, it&apos;s after school, which means no one is here! What&apos;s more, if someone saw us in such a place together...</Text>
  <Text Key="E57C3C7A_169275">Whatever... it doesn’t matter. None of that does. What matters right now...</Text>
  <Text Key="8892541B_169276">...Is that I’m alone here with you, Senpai.</Text>
  <Text Key="79C95BB5_169277">I don&apos;t care if it&apos;s just a dream. I’d never have the guts to do something like this... in the &quot;real world&quot;...</Text>
  <Text Key="B23EE41D_169278">...But. Someday... if I could muster even the slightest bit of courage...</Text>
  <Text Key="FE1E5A88_169279">....Pshyuuun....</Text>
  <Text Key="CFE3D28D_169280">AAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHH♪</Text>
  <Text Key="EB7CEDF4_169281">This!! THIS is what I was after☆ That was exactly the kind of thing I wanted to seeee~ I really outdid myself, good job~♪</Text>
  <Text Key="5831F6B7_169282">Weeeell... maybe I went just sliiiightly overboard with the hypnosis. She was kind of overflowing near the end...</Text>
  <Text Key="660EE4FE_169283">Anyway, you handle the cleanup, kay~♪ I&apos;ll watch the records of that log just to have another laugh~</Text>
  <Text Key="59597DBF_169284">Ugh! M-My head...!</Text>
  <Text Key="593F08CF_169285">...Eh? Kishi-san!? Why are you at my place...?</Text>
  <Text Key="24C67277_169286">...O-Oh, right... I asked him to come. I wanted to treat him to dinner.</Text>
  <Text Key="D21D3A5F_169287">...Oh, th-that&apos;s right! The Bandishark&apos;s door is...</Text>
  <Text Key="EB911C4A_169288">&quot;Too bad for youuu~♡ Still locked tighhhht~♡&quot;</Text>
  <Text Key="40009DC8_169289">Oh, come on... Fubuki-chan, really...?</Text>
  <Text Key="F44D547E_169290">Which means, I... fell asleep in front of Kishi-san? J-Just how careless can I...</Text>
  <Text Key="BCB410A8_169291">There&apos;s no graffiti in my face... Of course, he&apos;s not Fubuki-chan. Instead, he put a blanket on me...</Text>
  <Text Key="6CB0A433_169292">...I&apos;m sorry, Kishi-san. I fell asleep midway through offering you dinner...</Text>
  <Text Key="D43159FA_169293">After all, I have to keep an eye on you</Text>
  <Text Key="05B1B2A4_169294">...Y-Yes. You watched... my sleeping face... Ehehe...</Text>
  <Text Key="BE4BF987_169295">If I had been locked up alone... I would have been lonely. Having you here watching over me... it&apos;s a great help...♪</Text>
  <Text Key="21A59C12_169296">Well then, I&apos;m glad</Text>
  <Text Key="77A470B3_169297">Ehehe...</Text>
  <Text Key="F934EC2B_169298">...I-I said it. Even if we&apos;re not glued to each other like in that dream... I&apos;ve mustered up just a little bit of courage...</Text>
  <Text Key="8C3650A0_169299">To Fubuki-chan who created this situation... and to whoever created that dream... I&apos;m a little bit grateful, maybe...?</Text>
